Viewers all over the world, I am rescuing you from the fear of evil spirits
and fear of familiar spirits.
Be rescued in the name of Jesus!
Whatever spirit within and without, loose your grip!
Loose your grip!
Let my people go!
In the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Whatever disease in your faculties.
Whatever disease in your organ
and every pain be removed!
Begin to function!
Be it your blood, "begin to function!"
Be it your kidney "begin to function!"
Be it your bone, "begin to function!"
Be it your skin, "begin to function!"
Begin to function!
Your liver, kidney-begin to function. In the name of Jesus!
Rejoice!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Viewers all over the world, begin to count your blessings, I can see you being saved!
Begin to count your blessings, I can see you being delivered!
Begin to count your blessings, I can see you: being freed, being saved, and being healed!
Begin to count your blessings, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Count your blessings and give thanks to him!
Viewers all over the world, where can you go from his presence?
I say, "It is well!"
I say, "It is well with your soul!"
"It is well with your career!!"
"It is well with your life!"
I can hear, "it is well!"
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus name.
Thank you Lord! Thank you Lord! Thank you Lord! Thank you Lord! Thank you Lord!
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of Gods power in our generation today,
and stay up to date with the latest prophesies, deliverances, service, and testimonies.
From the Synagogue Church Of All Nations
Emmanuel TV. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.